It was naughty.
エッチでしたね
エッチでした
You say it like that.
あんなに言っちゃうんだね
yes.
はい
Do you always say things like that?
いつもあんなに言っちゃうの?
I'll say it.
言っちゃいます
But what don't you do?
でも何はしないの?
I don't.
しません
Really?
本当に?
I really don't.
本当にしません
From me, uh...
僕からね、あの...
A while ago, I was given various naughty looks,
さっきね、いろいろエッチな感じに見してもらったんで、
I thought I'd like to see something a little more naughty.
もっとね、ちょっとエッチなとこ見たいなと思ってまして
I also have a present for you, so please wear this if you'd like.
僕からプレゼントもあるんで、 よ かったらちょっとこれを着て
May I take your time and take your time?
いる ところを ゆっくり取らせてもらってもいいですか?
yes.
はい
What do you think?
何か思います?
picture?
え?
What is it?
何だろう?
Eh, what is it?
えー、なんだろう?
Like this, I'm wearing something that looks like cosplay.
こうやってさ、コスプレみたいの着てさ、
Have you ever had sex?
エッチしたりしたことあるのかな?
No.
ないです
It's my first time.
初めてです
That's right.
そうなんだ
I thought it would suit me.
似合うかなと思って
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I bought it, right?
買ってきたんだよね
Can I have you change your clothes while I'm changing?
着替えるところをさ、着替えしてもらってもいいかな?
What is this?
これは何ですか?
This, uh...
これはね、あの...
guess what?
何だと思う?
picture?
え?
This isn't it.
これじゃないし
picture?
え?
this is...
これは...
What is this?
何ですかこれ?
It's something to wear underneath.
下に履くものだね
I guess it's something to wear on top.
上に着るものじゃないかな
It's Star Juice, so it's difficult to wear.
スタージュースだからさ、着るのも難しいよね
Is it difficult?
難しいんですか?
It's fine as is.
このままでいい
It might be okay to leave it like this.
このままでいいかもね
You can keep your current pants.
今のパンツのままでいい
Does something suit you?
何か似合ってる?
Does it suit you?
似合ってます?
Hey, can you please take these pants off me?
ちょっと、このさ、 このパンツにどけてもらってもいいかな?
These pants?
このパンツ?
oh yeah.
そうそう
This is a little...
これちょっと...
It's transparent.
透けてるね
透けてますね
I don't like it.
嫌です
Let's go for a walk outside together, actually, like before.
一緒に外歩くか、 実はね、さっきみたいに、
Actually, I have another guy ready.
実はね、もう一人、 男の人用意してます
Another person?
もう一人?
Another person.
もう一人
Wait a minute, I'm calling you,
ちょっと、そしてね、 呼んでるから、
It's a bit naughty.
ちょっとエッチですね
But it suits you.
でも似合ってますね
Does it suit you?
似合ってます?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I wonder if I could take a picture a little bit forward.
ちょっと前進撮ってもいいかな
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
You're starting to look like a child, but just a little bit more.
子供みたいになってますけど、 もう ちょっとね、
Um, he's already come.
あのー、 もう来てくれました
Iida-kun.
飯田くん
Iida-kun?
飯田くん?
Mr. Iida.
飯田さん
Mr. Iida came.
飯田さん来てくれました
I have a busy schedule, but...
多忙なスケジュールなのがね、 ちょっと、
I'd like to film a one-on-one fight.
1対1のファイトをね、 ちょっと撮らせてもらいたいなって
yes.
はい
Can I call you for a moment?
ちょっと、呼んでもらってもいいですか?
yes.
はい
Mr. Iida.
飯田さん
This is Iida.
飯田です
What do you think?
どうですか?
Face to face.
対面は
I'm impressed, it's coming.
感動の、来てますよ
It's cute.
可愛いですね
Mr. Iida, you're sticking out a little.
飯田さん、ちょっと、 はみ出てますね
Excuse me for a moment.
すみません、ちょっと
It's so cute, it's so cute.
せっかくなんで、なかなかね、 可愛いんで、
I was sticking out, so that doesn't happen very often.
はみ出てたんで、 なかなかそういうこともないんで、
Let's do it this way for a moment.
ちょっと、こうやっておきますか
My favorite is Bangtan.
お気に入りバンタンですね
But is that what it is, a person who grows up?
でも、あれですか、 大きくなる人、
Do you hate it?
嫌いですか?
I like it already.
もう、好きです
One more time, this way.
ちょっと、もう一回、 こっちの方で
Do you hate people who get a little stiff?
ちょっと、硬くなる人、嫌いですか?
I like it.
好きです
It's smooth.
すべすべですね
Do you call it a baby doll?
ベ ビードールって言うんですか?
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
You asked me a question.
質問されちゃいましたね
This is nice.
これ、いいですね
Are you doing it?
やってます?
It's smooth.
滑らかですね
Is it silk?
シルクなのかな?
The feel.
肌触りが
I want to see your butt too.
お尻もね、 見たいですね
Butt?
お尻?
picture?
え?
That's a normal case.
普通の場合ですね
Only on my knees.
膝だけついて
Let's turn around from the left side.
左側から振り向いてみます
That's a cute butt.
かわいいお尻ですね
It's sturdy and has a lot of muscle inside.
し っかりと、中には 筋肉が しっかりと入ってます
Are you packed with muscles?
筋肉詰まってます?
Nice ass.
いいお尻
This is a butt that doesn't sag.
垂れないお尻ですよ、これ
I agree.
そうですね
Until the very last moment
ギリギリまで お尻
teeth.
は
Do you wear teabags?
テ ィーバックとか履きます?
I'll wear it.
履きます
tickles.
くすぐったい
Isn't it better to be rubbed properly?
しっかり揉まれるほうがいいんじゃない?
that's right.
そうです
Maybe you don't need a bra.
ブラジャーもしかすると いらないのかもしれないね
Is it because I put it in?
入れたせいの?
Shall we give it a try?
ちょっと試してみようか
That's what girls are all about.
女の子ってやつだよね
I'm still kneeling and my armpits are also included.
膝立ちのまま 脇も入ってます
Is there hair in it?
毛入ってる?
It's in.
入ってます
It's in there.
入ってるんです
Because I can't take it that far.
そこまで取れないから
He's standing up amazingly.
すごい一首立ってる
It's easy to stand.
立ちやすいよね
立ちやすいです
If your gender is male, does that mean you're violent?
性別が男だったら 暴気しまくってるってこと?
Probably so.
多分そうです
It feels good to have your neck played with.
一首いじられるの 気持ちいいね
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
I like this.
これ好きじゃん
It's almost upwards.
上向き近いだね
Your reaction is cute.
反応かわいいね
It makes me want to take a class that feels good.
気持ちいい授業したくなっちゃう
Is it easier to move around here?
こっちのほうも 動きしやすいの?
Maybe
もしかしたら
It's embarrassing to be seen.
見 られるの恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
It's smooth.
ツルツルだね
It's Joli Joli.
ジョリジョリです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
When you say that, it makes me want to see more.
そう言われると もっと見たくなってしまいます
what?
何?
It's very open.
すごい開いてる
It was a beautiful 50,000 pieces.
綺麗に 5万個でした
You came actively when we kissed.
キスするとき自分から積極的に来たね
I like kissing
キス好きな
of?
の?
It feels weird.
変 な感じ
yes.
はい
look?
見る?
I want to see it.
見たいよ
Shake it in front of me.
目の前で 振るね
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
thank you.
ありがとう
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
amazing.
すごい
nice.
いいね
There aren't many girls who are impressed by me.
なかなか感動してくれる女子いないね
Would you like me to observe your penis?
おちんちん観察してもらおうか、
Well then.
じゃあ
Picking things up, touching things, etc.
い ろいろつまんだりとか、触ったりとか
amazing.
すごい
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
amazing.
すごい
Why did you smell it?
なんで匂い嗅いだの?
I thought it didn't smell.
匂いがしないと思って
I'm kind of happy, so far.
なんか嬉しいな、ここまで
He said he would do all kinds of things for me.
い ろいろしてくれると
So beautiful.
すごい 綺麗
Looks like chilizao.
チリザオみたい
Chilizao.
チリザオ
amazing.
すごい
Would you like to go straight to the mouth?
そのままお口の方行ってみますか?